=Episode 16=
(Ferrying Souls Across Oblivion)
(Six Steps)
(Forget Your Past)
Forget my past?
No.
I can't forget Eryue.
(Cross the River of Oblivion)
(Be Cast into Unending Hell)
(Never to Be Reincarnated)
Let go of me!
I can't forget Eryue.
Eryue.
Why are you here?
Were you waiting for me?
How dare you!
Eryue.
Why are you doing this to me?
Weren't we once in love?
Silence!
Deities and mortals belong
to different worlds.
How could a deity
long for a mortal?
A deity?
That's impossible.
My true name is Yellow Dragon.
I am the Deity of Zhongtu.
Everything you have
was a gift from me.
And yet you're still not satisfied.
So all of this
was part of your plan.
Were your feelings for me fake too?
Yes.
My heart belongs to all living beings.
I could never devote it to just one.
So I advise you to stop
clinging to this hopeless obsession.
Cross the river now.
Move on to your next life.
I understand.
Since you don't love me,
why should I keep clinging to you?
I'm leaving.
Yellow Dragon.
Did you know
I've always seen through your lies?
You have your reasons in this life.
I won't force you.
In our next life,
you must come find me.
Liuyue.
I interfered with your fate
and caused your tragic death today.
Forget me.
You still have countless lives ahead.
You can still...
find someone worthy of you again.
Since you love her so much,
I'll make you
watch her suffer
while you can do nothing.
Then,
you'll die in agony.
Don't touch her!
Demon-Suppressing Seal.
Break!
(Once the seal is broken,)
(Demonic Energy will enter your body
and turn you into a demon.)
(There will be no turning back.)
Anyone who harms Xi Yuan
dies.
Did you
send her away?
In the end,
just as we intended,
their love remained unfulfilled,
and death tore them apart.
But now,
it all seems unbearably cruel.
But we can't turn back.
We mustn't turn back.
- Such powerful Demonic Energy.
Interesting. Very interesting.
Still,
falling into demonic corruption
must be painful, right?
Spatial Severance.
- Nine Nether Soul Devour!
- Ten Deaths, No Survival!
- Soul-Destroying Formation!
Since you used Demonic Energy,
you'll pay the price.
Jin Yunlie.
This Soul-Destroying Formation
was specifically used
against Demon Clan traitors.
Now,
it's perfect for you.
In less than fifteen minutes,
your soul will be obliterated.
Jin Yunlie!
Xi Yuan!
(Is doing this for him)
(really worth it?)
Who would've thought
that after ten million years,
I'd witness a sight like this?
This is
truly satisfying.
You're not Xi Yuan.
You're...
If that's true,
then you must be
Xi Yuan's former incarnation.
You shouldn't have betrayed me.
You've fallen into demonhood,
and my Phoenix Primordial Flame
is the bane of Demonic Energy.
It's time to settle
the score between us.
They're
turning on each other.
Isn't that even better?
Once Jin Yunlie is dead,
we can sit back and reap the rewards.
If I truly harmed you,
then kill me.
I won't resent you.
But I need to know.
Will Xi Yuan come back?
You have no right to care about her.
Once you're dead,
she'll come back.
That's good.
You must
get her
out of here safely.
It's not him.
No.
Impossible.
That face...
I could never mistake it.
Die!
No!
Don't hurt him!
Xi Yuan.
I'm helping you.
Why are you resisting me?
Helping me?
Who are you?
Why do you look exactly like me?
I am you,
and you are me.
Ten thousand years ago,
we were the Phoenix Deity.
We
were betrayed
and killed
by the Huyun Deity.
Today,
I'm avenging us.
The Huyun Deity?
You mean
Jin Yunlie?
How is that possible?
He's just an ordinary man.
He can't be the Huyun Deity.
Jin Yunlie?
Is that his new name?
Even if he changed his appearance
and remade his entire body,
I will never forget him.
Fine.
If you've forgotten that memory,
I'll help you remember it.
Really?
That's wonderful.
Yes.
Except...
you have to die.
This...
Is that me with him?
♪A love letter, a passionate pursuit♪
♪The envy of everyone♪
♪Bouquets and heartfelt confessions♪
♪Leaving me moved and fulfilled♪
♪No matter how long or hard our road♪
♪I don't care♪
♪But you left me with this pain♪
♪Forever beyond redemption♪